<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Forensics on Noé Backert | Blog</title><link>https://www.noe.backert.fr/tags/forensics/</link><description>Recent content in Forensics on Noé Backert | Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.156.0</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.noe.backert.fr/tags/forensics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Windows - LDAP User As_RepRoastable</title><link>https://www.noe.backert.fr/ctf/ldapuserasreproastable/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.noe.backert.fr/ctf/ldapuserasreproastable/</guid><description>During the investigation, you obtain a backup of the company LDAP directory generated with ldap2json. Use the information contained in this dump to identify the ASRepRoastable user.</description></item><item><title>LDAP User Kerberoastable</title><link>https://www.noe.backert.fr/ctf/ldapuserkerberoastable/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.noe.backert.fr/ctf/ldapuserkerberoastable/</guid><description>During your investigation, you recover an LDAP directory backup exported using ldap2json. Use the information contained in this dump to identify the Kerberoastable user.</description></item><item><title>Trouvez le Chat</title><link>https://www.noe.backert.fr/ctf/trouvezlechat/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.noe.backert.fr/ctf/trouvezlechat/</guid><description>A forensic challenge involving a FAT filesystem where deleted web artifacts and a document must be recovered using filesystem analysis and file carving techniques to ultimately extract hidden metadata.</description></item><item><title>Silicon Data Sleuthing</title><link>https://www.noe.backert.fr/ctf/silicondatasleuthing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:50:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.noe.backert.fr/ctf/silicondatasleuthing/</guid><description>In the dust and sand surrounding the vault, you unearth a rusty PCB... You try to read the etched print, it says Open...W...RT, a router! You hand it over to the hardware gurus and to their surprise the ROM Chip is intact! They manage to read the data off the tarnished silicon and they give you back a firmware image. It&amp;#39;s now your job to examine the firmware and maybe recover some useful information that will be important for unlocking and bypassing some of the vault&amp;#39;s countermeasures!</description></item><item><title>Driver's Shadow</title><link>https://www.noe.backert.fr/ctf/driversshadow/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.noe.backert.fr/ctf/driversshadow/</guid><description>A critical Linux server began behaving erratically under suspected Volnaya interference, so a full memory snapshot was captured for analysis. Stealthy components embedded in the dump are altering system behavior and hiding their tracks; your task is to sift through the snapshot to uncover these concealed elements and extract any hidden payloads.</description></item></channel></rss>